Hello, friend.
你好 朋友
"Hello, friend." That's lame.
"你好 朋友" 這么說太遜了
Maybe I should give you a name, but that's a slippery slope.
也許我應該給你取一個名字 但是這會讓我們陷入難以解釋的困境
You're only in my head. We have to remember that.
你只存在于我的腦海中 我們必須得銘記這點
Shit. It's actually happened,
媽的 這種事情真的發生了
I'm talking to an imaginary person.
我在和一個想象中的人交談
What I'm about to tell you is top secret,
我要告訴你的是最高機密
a conspiracy bigger than all of us.
一個超乎我們所有人意想的陰謀
There's a powerful groupof people out there
在此之外 有一群極富權勢的人
that are secretly running the world.
在秘密地操控著這個世界
I'm talking about the guys no one knows about,
沒有人知道他們我所說的這些人
the guys that are invisible.
這些家伙是無處可見的
The top 1% of the top 1%,
他們是頂尖的那1%人中的1%
the guys that play God without permission.
不需要誰允許 他們就能扮演上帝
And now I think they're following me.
而現在我覺得他們在跟蹤我
This is about last night.
這些都和昨晚有關
I should've gone to Angela's birthday party.
我本應該去安吉拉的生日派對
Instead, I went to--
相反 我去了--
Hey, Ron.
嗨 羅恩
There you go.
給
You're Ron.
你是羅恩
But your real name is Rohit Mehta.
但是你的真名是羅希特 每塔
You changed it to Ron when you bought
你把它改成了羅恩 就在你六年前
your first Ron's Coffee Shop six years ago.
買下你的第一家羅恩的咖啡店的時候
Now you got 17 of 'em,with 8 more coming next quarter.
現在你有了17家分店 下一季度還會開8家新店
May I help you with something?
我能幫你做些什么嗎?
I like coming here 'cause your Wi-Fi was fast.
我喜歡來這兒 因為你這兒的無線網很快
I mean, you're one of the few spots
我的意思是 你這兒是為數不多的幾個
that has a fiber connection with gigabit speed.
用光纖連接 能達到千兆位速度的地方之一
It's good. So good, it scratched
這很好 特別好 它觸動了
that part of my mind, part that doesn't allow good to exist
我心里的一部分 那一部分關于好的事情
without condition,so I started intercepting
不該無緣無故出現的想法 所以我開始攔截
all the traffic on your network.
你網絡中的所有通信量
That's when I noticed something strange.
這時候我注意到有些蹊蹺
It's when I decided to hack you.
也就是那個時候我決定黑了你
- Hack--
- 黑了--
-I know you run a website called Plato's Boys.
我知道你在經營一個叫"柏拉圖的男孩"的網站
- Pardon me?
不好意思?
You're using Tor networking
你在用洋蔥路由網絡
to keep the servers anonymous.
來使你的服務器保持匿名
You made it really hard for anyone to see it,
你為了不讓別人看到 確實在這兒費了一番功夫
but I saw it.
但是我看到了
The onion routing protocol,
洋蔥路由協定
it's not as anonymous  as you think it is.
并沒有你想象中的那么能隱姓埋名
Whoever's in control of the exit nodes
不論是誰 只要被已存在的節點管理
is also in control of the traffic,
也會被網絡通信所掌握
which makes me... the one in control.
這也就讓我成為... 能夠掌控這些的人
I must ask you to kindly leave.
我必須禮貌地請你離開
I own everything.
我掌握了一切
All your emails. All your files.
你所有的郵件 你所有的文檔
All your...pics.
你所有的...圖片
Get out of here right now, or I'll call the--
馬上從這兒滾出去 否則我要叫...
Police? You want them to find out
警察? 你希望他們發現
about the 100 terabytes of child pornography
你提供給你的40萬用戶的那些超過
you serve to your 400,000 users?
100千兆字節的兒童色情片么?
Personally, man, I was hoping it was just gonna be
就我個人來說 哥們兒 我會希望這不過是些
some BDSM stuff.
捆綁性虐一類的東西
You realize how much simpler that would have been?
你知道那樣 事情會簡單多少么?
I did not hurt anyone.
我沒有傷害任何人
I never did.
我從沒傷害過
That's my... personal life.
那是我的... 個人生活
I understand what it's like
我很理解和別人不一樣
to be different.
是什么感覺
I'm very different too.
我也很不一樣
I mean, I don't jerk off to little kids, but...
我的意思是 我不會對著小孩手淫 只不過...
I don't know how to talk to people.
我不懂得如何和人交流
My dad was the only one I could talk to.
我爸爸是我唯一能夠進行交流的人
But he died.
但是他死了
I'm sorry to hear that.
我很抱歉聽到這個消息
How did he pass,
我能問問
may I ask?
他是怎么死的么?
Leukemia.
白血病
He definitely got it from radiation
他得病毫無疑問是因為他工作的
at the company he worked at,
公司里的那些輻射
though I couldn't prove it.
雖然我沒有辦法證明這一點
Now he's dead.
現在他死了
Company's fine, though.
不過公司還好好的
Oh...hey.
哦... 嘿
It's okay, Rohit.
沒關系 羅希特
You don't have to worry anymore.
你不需要擔心了
I don't understand.
我沒聽懂
Are you blackmailing me?
你是在敲詐我么?
So that's what this is about...
所以這一切都是關于...
money.
錢
That's all you care about, huh?
這就是你想要的 哈?
No.
不行
If I pay you now,you'll want more and more.
如果我現在付錢給你 你就會越要越多
No matter how much I give.
無論我給你多少
You will inform the police anyway.
你都會告訴警察的
I won't pay you, sir.
我不會付錢給你的 先生
Remember, you also broke the law.
記住 你也違反了法律
Actually, you're right.
事實上 你講對了
Partly.
只講對了一部分
See, I usually do this kind of thing
是這樣 我通常是在我的電腦上
from my computer,
做這些事情
but this time I wanted to do it  AFK.
但是這次我想脫離電腦來做
In person.
親自當面做
Trying to work on my social anxiety.
努力來克服我的社交焦慮
But there's always the threat of you fleeing
不過在我把你叫出來以后 總是會有
after I call you out.
你會逃跑的威脅存在
You'd tell your sys admin
你會告訴你的系統管理員
to take your servers down,wipe all the data.
關閉你的服務器 抹掉所有數據
So I made sure to include
所以我保證
the current time and location
我的匿名舉報中 會包含現在的時間
on my anonymous tip.
還有地點
Wait. Hold on.
等一下 別走
I'll give you the money.
我給你錢
I'll pay you.
我付你錢
How much do you want?
你想要多少?
That's the part you were wrong about, Rohit.
這就是你想錯的那部分 羅希特
I don't give a shit about money.
我才不在乎什么鳥錢
Now I'm being followed.
現在我被跟蹤了
The higher ups don't like someone with my powers.
高層的人不喜歡有我這樣能力的人
In three short minutes,
在短短的三分鐘里
I destroyed a man's business,life, existence.
我毀掉了一個男人的事業 生活和存在
- I deleted him.
我刪除了他
- Hey!
嘿!
Hey, you.
嘿 你
Hey, kiddo.
嘿 小孩兒
What's happening?
發生什么了?
Exciting time in the world right now.
現在正是這個世界上激動人心的時期
Exciting time.
激動人心的時期
But I'm only a vigilante hacker by night.
可是我只是一個黑夜里維護秩序的黑客
By day, just a regular
在白天 不過是一個普通的
cyber security engineer,
網絡安全工程師
employee number ER28-0652.
員工編號 ER28-0652
Elliot!
伊利艾特!
In here.
這兒
- What's up?
怎么了?
- El.
伊爾
Yeah, I can totally-- I can totally handle it.
好了 我完全能 我完全能搞定這個
They were hacked again.
他們又被黑了了
Last night.
昨天晚上
Gideon...
吉迪恩...
That's my childhood friend Angela.
那個是我的發小安吉拉
She can be a bit high strung sometimes,
她有時候會神經兮兮的
but trust me-- she's one of the good ones.
但是相信我 她是好人一個
What am I looking at?
我看的這是什么?
Is this the log file?
是訪客記錄文檔么?
This was a RUDY attack.
這是一次RUDY攻擊
This is awesome.
真是太棒了
- Gideon, will you answer me?
吉迪恩 你能不能回答我?
- Awesome?
太棒了?
You think this is awesome? This is killing us, Elliot.
你覺得這很棒? 這會弄死我們的 伊利艾特
- Gideon, I'm not-- - Angela!
- 吉迪恩 我不是 - 安吉拉!
Let's just see how this meeting goes today.
我們還是看看今天這個會怎么開吧
Their networks are getting attacked every week.
他們的網絡每周都會遭到攻擊
Who knows if they'll still even be a client.
誰知道他們會不會愿意繼續做我們的顧客
They're coming in? Hey, what did we say
他們黑進來了? 嘿 我們是怎么說的
about the dress code?
員工著裝要求?
All right, now,look over those logs.
好吧 現在看完那些記錄
And be ready this afternoon in case they have any questions.
然后下午要準備好以防他們有任何問題
Okay?
好么?
Okay.
好的
- Start smoking again? - Did you not get
- 又開始抽煙了? - 你昨天晚上
my texts last night?
是不是沒收到我的短信?
I sent you exactly 13 of them.
我實打實地給你發了13條
Yeah, I'm sorry.
啊 我很抱歉
I couldn't make it.
我沒能去成
You promised me that you were
你答應過我
gonna try this time.
你這次會試試的
Stop thinking about something else
當我和你說話的時候
when I'm talking to you.
不要想別的事情
I hate when you do that.
我討厭你那么做
Sorry. I was thinking about work.
對不起 我是在想工作的事情
Maybe that's why Gideon oves you so much.
也許這就是為什么吉迪恩這么愛你的原因吧
He thanks me all the time for bringing you in.
他一直感謝我引薦了你
But for some reason,
但是不知道為什么
I think you secretly hate it here.
我覺得你私下里很討厭這兒
She was right.
她說對了
I liked most of the people,
我更喜歡這兒的人
but our business, a cyber security firm
而不是我們保護大集團的
that protects corporations--
網絡安全公司的這份工作
I can't think of anything I hate more.
我想不出比這更討厭的事情了
No, I love it here.
不是啊 我喜歡這兒
I'm sorry.
不好意思
I'm just in a bad mood.
我只是心情不大好
I'm late on my last
我已經拖延支付了
two student loan payments,
最近的兩筆助學貸款還款
and I can't get Gideon to give me a raise.
我也不能讓吉迪恩給我加薪
Yo, buddy.
呦 哥們兒
Missed you last night.
昨晚上沒見你
Where were you?
你去哪了?
Gotta go.
我走了
Big meeting today.
今天的會很重要
Did you find out what happened?
你搞明白發生什么了嗎?
Yeah. He said he was working.
嗯 他說他在工作
Oh, come on.
哦 得了吧
You gotta talk to him.
你得和他談談
We're gonna be late for the staff meeting.
我們要在員工大會上遲到了
He can't stand me.
他根本就受不了我
And you know why.
而你知道為什么
Angela, I can't have
安吉拉 我不能夠
that kind of negativity in my life.
讓我的生活中有那樣的負能量
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
這才是我要說的
What are you thinking about?
你在想什么啊?
Nothing.
沒什么
You want to know what I'm thinking about?
你想知道 我在想什么嗎?
First time you came to me.
你第一次來找我的時候
I didn't exactly come to Krista.
準確說我并不是去找克里斯塔
I was forced here.
我是被逼去的
But I do like her.
不過我的確喜歡她
Hacking her was simple.
黑她的電腦很容易
Her password: Dylan 2791.
她的密碼是 Dylan 2791
Favorite artist and the year in
最欣賞的藝術家和
which she was born, backwards.
她出生的年份倒過來
Though she's a psychologist,
雖然她是個心理醫生
she's really bad
但她讀人的能力
at reading people.
實在是差勁
But I'm good at reading people.
不過我很擅長讀人
I look for
我看得到
the worst in them.
他們最糟糕的一面
I know she went through
我知道她四年前
a divorce four years ago.
經歷了一次離婚
I know she was devastated by it
我知道她曾因此精神崩潰
and has been dating losers
還從那后在百合網上
on eHarmony ever since.
和些窩囊廢約會
Her most recent foray--
她最近的囊中物是--
Michael Hansen.
邁克爾 漢森
I searched for him online,but nothing came up.
我在網上搜索了他 但是一無所獲
No LinkedIn, no Facebook,nothing.
沒有領英網資料 沒有臉書 干干凈凈
Something about him bugs me,
他的一些事情困擾著我
scratching that part  of my mind again.
又一次觸動了我心里的一部分
But I'll hack him soon enough.I always do.
但是我很快就能黑他了 我總能黑別人
I know you're not yelling like before,
我知道你已經不像以前那樣大喊大叫了
which is good.
這很好
But I can tell you're still holding on to it.
但是我能察覺到你還是不能釋懷
And we need to work on your anger issues, Elliot.
我們需要解決你的暴躁易怒 伊利艾特
You're angry at everyone, at society...
你對每個人 對社會都心懷憤恨...
Fuck society.
操你媽的社會
I know you have a lot to be angry about,
我知道你有很多可憤怒的事情
but keeping it to yourself and staying quiet
但是要壓制在自己內心里 保持冷靜
like you're doing--it's not going to help you.
像你現在這樣這樣是對你自己沒有幫助的
There's pain underneath.
在表象下的痛苦
That's where our work needs to go.
這才是我們需要解決的問題
What is it about society that disappoints you so much?
這個社會怎么讓你這么不滿呢?
Oh, I don't know.
哦 我不知道
Is it that we collectively thought Steve Jobs
是因為我們都覺得史蒂夫 喬布斯
was a great man, even when we knew
是個偉大的人 即使是我們都知道
he made billions off the backs of children?
他的數十億資產是因為童工才得以成功?
Or maybe it's that it feels like all our heroesare counterfeit.
或者是因為似乎我們所有的英雄偶像都是偽君子
The world itself's just one big hoax.
世界本身就是一個巨大的騙局
Spamming with our running commentary of bullshit
發各種狗屁實況轉播的垃圾郵件
masquerading as insight, our social media faking as intimacy.
偽裝自己的內心 我們的社交媒體都在假裝親密
Or is it that we voted for this?
還是我們自己選擇了這些?
Not with our rigged elections,but with our things,
不是通過作弊選舉 而是通過我們自己的東西
our property, our money.
自己的財產 自己的錢財
I'm not saying anything new.
我所講的都不是新聞
We all know why we do this,
我們都知道自己為什么這么做
not because Hunger Games books makes us happy
不是因為饑餓游戲的書籍讓我們覺得開心
but because we wanna be sedated.
是因為我們想要沉著下來
Because it's painful not to pretend,
因為這份苦痛不用假裝
because we're cowards.
因為我們都是膽小鬼
Fuck society.
操你媽的社會
Elliot. Elliot.
伊利艾特 伊利艾特
You're not saying anything.
你什么也不說
What's wrong?
這是怎么了?
Nothing.
沒什么
Don't be frustrated.
別泄氣
Why shouldn't I be?
我為什么不應該泄氣
You're different than most.
你和大多數人都不一樣
You at least try.
至少你努力了
You at least understand.
至少你懂得了
Understand what?
懂什么了?
What it's like to feel alone.
孤獨的滋味
You understand the pain.
你懂得這種苦痛
You want to protect people from it.
你想要保護人們遠離苦痛
You want to protect me from it.
你想要保護我遠離苦痛
I respect that about you.
我敬重你這一點
Why do you think I know what it's like to feel alone?
你為什么覺得我懂得孤獨的滋味?
Shit! From her emails!
媽的! 從她的郵件知道的!
Elliot?
伊利艾特?
I don't know.
我也不知道
Let's talk about last night.
我們來說說昨天晚上
Did you go to Angela's birthday party?
你去安吉拉的生日派對了嗎?
Yeah. It was nice.
去了 辦的不錯
Did you try to talk to anyone?
你有沒有試著和什么人講話?
Sure.
當然
I got a girl's number.
我要到了一個女孩的號碼
You did?
你要到了號碼?
She's cute.
她很漂亮
She likes The Hunger Games.
她很喜歡饑餓游戲
You're hiding again, Elliot.
你又在隱藏自己了 伊利艾特
When you hide, your delusions come back.
你隱藏自己的時候 你的錯覺就又出來了
It's a slippery slope.
這是一種滑坡效應
Let's talk about the men in black you've been seeing.
我們來講講你一直能看到的那些黑衣人
Are they still there?
他們還在那嗎?
No, I... told you they're gone.
沒有了 我 告訴你他們都消失了
The meds you gave me are working.
你給我的藥起作用了
Yo, man.
喲 老兄
Do you wanna, uh...
你想要 額...
you wanna do lunch today?
你想要今天一起吃午飯嗎?
Uh, yeah...
額 恩...
-I got other plans.-Other plans. Right.
-我有約了 -有約了 對啊
That's...what you said the last three times I asked you.
前... 前三次我問你的時候你也是這么說的
Look, bud, you...
聽著 老兄 你....
and Angela have been close
和安吉拉一直以來都很親近
for a long time, and that's even more reason why I want us to be on good terms.
這是我想要和你搞好關系的更為重要的理由
I-I just--I feel like things have been awkward between us.
我 我就是 就是覺得我們兩個之間有點尷尬
Don't you?
你不覺得嗎?
I'm okay with it being awkward between us.
我覺得我們兩個之間尷尬沒所謂
Um, yeah.
額 好吧
I-I'm--I'm not okay with that.
我 我 我覺得這樣有所謂
Um...look, man, I love Angela,
額.. 聽著 老兄 我愛安吉拉
and I want us to-- to get along for her sake.
我想我們兩個看在她的份上好好相處
I mean, that's what I'm-- that's what I'm here for.
我的意思是 這是我 這是我此時此刻在這的原因
I just, I... I don't normally do stuff...
我就是 我通常不做這樣的...
Am I crazy not to like this guy?
我不喜歡這個人太神經質了嗎?
Among some of his Facebook likes
他的臉書點贊的有
are George W. Bush's Decision Points,
喬治W布什的 決策時刻
Transformers 2: Revenge of the Fallen,
變形金剛2: 卷土重來
and the music of Josh Groban.
喬詩葛洛班的音樂
Must I really justify myself any further?
我還要更進一步證明我的想法?
I'm working on that shit, you know?
我還在攻克這些狗鋪 你知道嗎?
His was the easiest to hack. Password was 123456Seven.
他是最容易黑的人 密碼是123456七
I witnessed his first "I love you" With Angela over Gchat,
我見證了他通過微信對安吉拉說的第一句"我愛你"
then I witnessed the first of many infidelities with Stella B.
接著我又見證了第一次偷偷與史黛拉B出軌
I've never done anything like this before...I've thought about telling Angela,
我從來沒有做過這樣的事...我想過要告訴安吉拉
but she has shitty taste in men,
但是她對男人的品位跟屎一樣
and I'm not quite ready to see what comes after this just yet.
而且我也沒有準備好看看接下來會發生什么
You like music. I like music.
你喜歡音樂 我喜歡音樂
Maroon 5.
魔力紅
Plus I can manage Ollie easier than the others.
而且奧利比起其他人更容易被我控制
for now, anyway.
不管怎么說 至少現在是這樣
And that's all I mean.
我就是這個意思
I just want you to know that.
我就是想要你知道
I like you, bro, and...
我喜歡你 兄弟 而且...
I want you to like me too.
我也想要你喜歡我
I understand.
我理解
I'll try harder.
我會更加努力的
That's cool, man.
沒關系的 老兄
Hey, whenever you're ready, I'd love to just...
嘿 不管你什么時候準備好了 我都愿意...
chill.
被你震一下
Oh--forgot about your... no touching thing.
哦 忘了你 不愿意被人碰
Truth is, I shouldn't hate Ollie; he's not that bad a guy.
事實上 我不應該討厭奧利 他不是個很壞的人
He's too dumb to be bad.
他太蠢不夠格當壞人
In fact, when I think about the really bad people...
事實上 當我想到非常壞的人...
E Corp, the largest conglomerate in the world...
E公司 世界上最大的綜合企業
they're so big,
企業之大
they're literally everywhere.
他們真的是無處不在
A perfect monster of modern society.
真是現代社會最完美的妖魔
-The E might as well stand for Evil. -And all of life's necessities...
-E可能是代表邪惡 -所有的生命所需
In fact, after a thorough,intensive self-reprogramming,
事實上 經過一番徹底的精密的自我編程
that's all my mind hears, sees, or reads
這就是我所聽到 看到 讀到的
-when they pop up in my world. -That was have to offer.
-當他們突然出現在我的世界里 -這就是必須要提供的
Together, we can change the world,
眾志成城 我們就能改變世界
with E-- Evil Corp.
E- 邪惡公司
Krista would have a shit fit if she knew I did that.
如果克里斯塔知道我這么做肯定會被嚇得不輕
But that's what they are-- a conglomerate of evil.
但是這就是他們的本質 一家邪惡大企業
And now I have to help them.
現在我不得不幫助他們
There are six on-site engineers on your account.
負責您公司的有6位在線工程師
- Plus a few off-site...- There he is, Terry Colby,the CTO.
- 加上幾位線下... - 就是他 泰利 科爾比  首席技術官
Even though he's the head technology guy at one of the biggest companies in the world,
雖然他是世界上最大公司之一的技術人員頭目
he owns a Blackberry.
他還是用黑莓
So this is it right here.
所以目前為止就是這樣
But also looks like he doesn't see a terminal very often
而且看起來好像他不經常用電腦
He's not a techie. He's a moron.
他不是個技術專家 他是個腦殘
An arrogant moron.
一個傲慢的腦殘
The worst kind.
最差勁的那種
Oh, hi. Tyrell Wellick.
哦 嗨 我是提瑞爾 威力克
I'm Senior Vice President, Technology.
我是科技部高級副總裁
Elliot. Just a tech.
伊利艾特 我就是個技術工
Don't be so humble.
別這么謙虛
You know, I started out exactly where you are,
要知道 我也是從你這個位子起家的
and...to be honest, you know,my heart is still there.
而且 實話說 你知道的 我的心還在這里呢
So I see you're running Gnome.
我看你在運行Gnome啊
You know, I'm actually on KDE myself.
你知道 我自己其實還在用KDE
I know this desktop environment is supposed to be better but...
我知道你的這個桌面環境應該更完善的 但是
you know what they say.
你也知道他們怎么說
Old habits-- they die hard.
舊習難改
An executive running Linux with--
一個行政人員運行Linux
Yeah, I know what you're thinking.
恩 我知道你在想什么
I'm an executive. I mean...
我是個行政人員 我是說
why am I even running Linux?
我為什么要運行Linux呢?
Again--old habits.
再說一遍 是因為舊習
It's gonna be fun working with you.
和你一起工作肯定很有趣
I should join the rest of the group.
我該去找我的團隊了
Bonsoir, Elliot.
再見 伊利艾特
Sometimes I dream of saving the world.
有時候我夢想拯救世界
Saving everyone from the invisible hand,
拯救每個人逃脫無形的手
one that brands us with an employee badge.
那只用員工證歸類我們的手
The one that forces us to work for them...
那只迫使我們為他們工作的手
The one that controls us every day without us knowing it.
那只每天控制著我們而我們卻不自知的手
But I can't stop it.
但是我無法阻止它
I'm not that special.
我并不那樣特殊
I'm just anonymous.
我只是個無名小卒
I'm just alone.
我踽踽獨行
If it weren't for Qwerty,
如果不是為了庫爾提
I'd be completely empty.
我會變得徹底空虛
I hate when I can't hold in my loneliness.
我恨我難抑內心空虛的時候
This crying has been happening too often,
哭泣得太頻繁
every other week now.
現在每隔一周發作一次
What do normal people do when they get this sad?
當正常的人這樣難過的時候都做什么?
They reach out to friends or family, I think.
他們聯系朋友或家人 我是這么覺得的
That's not an option.
我沒有這種選擇
I do morphine.
我只能嗑嗎啡
The key to doing morphine without turning into a junkie
嗑嗎啡而又不會把自己變成癮君子的關鍵在于
is to limit yourself to 30 milligrams a day.
每天限食30毫克
Anything more just builds up your tolerance.
再多的吸食就會產生藥物耐受性
I check every pill I get for purity.
我核查了每片藥的純度
I have 8 milligram Suboxone for maintenance
我有8毫克的納洛酮以維持
in case I go through withdrawals.
以防我退癮
Shit! I'm out again.
媽的! 我又用完了
How much?
多少錢？
On the house.
我請了
No, Shayla.
不 夏拉
Not doing that.
別這樣
Okay? This is just
好嗎? 這只是一個
a regular drug deal
普通的毒品交易
like it always is.
就像我們之前做的
Fine.
好吧
So what are you up to tonight?
所以你今晚要做什么?
'Cause I tried to post
我嘗試在
something on your Facebook
你的臉書上發點東西
and couldn't find you.
但是我沒有找到你
I'm not on Facebook.
我沒有臉書賬號
What? Why not?
什么? 為啥?
'Cause I hate Facebook.
因為我討厭臉書
That's crazy.
這太不正常了
Well...you want to
那你今晚想不想
do these together then?
一起吸點這個?
Pure Molly...
純搖頭丸哦...
Don't ever make decisions when you're on morphine.
永遠不要在你嗑藥之后做決定
Instagram check-in
Instagram上顯示克里斯塔
for Krista at Pierre Loti.
去了綠蒂酒吧
Okay, Michael Hansen.
好的 邁克爾 漢森
Time to find out who you really are.
是時候該查明你到底是誰了
Thank you. Bye.
謝謝你 再見
Taxi!
出租車!
Uh, hi--I just left
喂 你好 我剛剛把
my keys in one of your cabs.
我的鑰匙落在你們的出租車上了
56Y2.
56Y2
Sure.
好的
What about you two?
你們兩個怎么說?
You guys got any
你們有沒有
spare change?
多余的零錢?
Help me out?
來幫我解決溫飽問題？
New York's expensive, guys.
紐約人都很有錢的 朋友們
Come on.
施舍一點吧
306 Hawthorne.
霍桑街306號
Thank you.Thank you.
謝謝你 非常感謝你
Come on, asshole
快點 笨蛋
Piss already.
已經噓噓過了
Come on!
快點
Will you--will you go?
你...你不想走嗎？
Come on, go, go! Go, will ya?
快點 我們走啊 走 你不是要走嗎？
Hey.
嘿
May I borrow your phone?
我可以借一下你的手機嗎?
Mine's dead.
我的沒電了
I need to call my mom.
我需要給我媽媽打個電話
Thank you.
謝謝你了
No answer.
沒人接
Thanks anyway.
還是謝謝你了
Angela,is everything okay?
安吉拉 有事嗎?
I need you to come to AllSafe.
我需要你來公司一下
You're there?
你在那?
It's 3:00 in the morning.
現在可是凌晨三點
They attacked Evil Corp
他們又一次攻擊了邪惡公司
servers again,
的服務器
but it's bad this time.
這次要嚴重的多
It's a DDoS attack.
這次是分布式拒絕服務攻擊
Did you call Lloyd? He's on call.
你給羅伊德打電話了嗎? 現在該他值班
Yeah, he's here.
對 他現在在這里
Is he talking to their tech department?
他跟公司的技術部門聯系過了嗎?
He's online with them,
他現在在跟他們線上交流
but so far nothing.
但是目前一無所獲
I don't think that
我不覺得
Lloyd can handle this.
羅伊德能夠解決這個問題
Look, Gideon just put me on this account.
聽著 吉迪恩剛剛把我調到這里來
I can't screw up
我不能才工作一周
in my first week.
就把事情搞砸了
I need you.
我需要你
Please.
拜托了
Finally!
終于來了
Calm down it's only been an hour.
冷靜 這才一個小時
Yeah, well, an hour in Evil Corp time is like $13 million in revenue, approximately.
當然 一個小時對邪惡公司來說可是大約1300萬美元的收入
Actually,
實際上
I calculated that.
我計算過了
That's exactly how much they lost.
這就是他們損失的錢數
Don't worry.
不要擔心
I got you.
我來幫你了
Lloyd, what's up?
羅伊德 怎么樣了?
Lloyd!
羅伊德!
Elliot. This is bad.
伊利艾特 情況很糟糕
Worst DDoS attack I've ever seen.
這是我見過的最棘手的分布式拒絕服務攻擊
Did you reconfigure the DNS?
你能夠重新辨別域名嗎?
Yes!
可以
Stop the services.
終止服務
I already stopped the services, tries to reboot the servers
我已經終止了所有的服務 現在在嘗試重啟服務器
but they're not coming back up.
但是現在不能夠啟動服務器了
Dude, someone is straight up fingerblasting their entire network right now.
伙計 現在有人正在著手攻擊他們的整個網絡 就在現在
They just started reporting on the outage.
已經有相關報道了
Shit. This is worse than I thought.
該死 這比我想的還要糟
They're in the network?
他們現在在網上?
What's the status update?
現在是什么情況?
I thought we set up security protocols
我以為我們有設置網絡安全協議呢
so that this doesn't happen.
所以這個不會發生
Where's the attack coming from?
這個攻擊源自哪里?
Everywhere, obviously.
很顯然 是從各個地方
The USA, Finland, Thailand, Kuwait--
美國 芬蘭 泰國 科威特
Start restarting the services, load sharing, redirect the traffic. Call Prolexic for help.
開始重啟所有的服務器 開始共享 重定所有的數據流量 叫Prolexic幫忙
What?
怎么了?
I don't think this is just a DDoS attack.
我不覺得這只是一次分布式拒絕服務攻擊那么簡單
I think they got a rootkit sitting inside the servers.
我覺得他們已經獲得了一個隱匿程式 現在已經侵入到了整個服務器中了
What's a rootkit?
什么是隱匿程式?
It's like a crazy serial rapist with a very big dick.
它就像是一個有著大屌的瘋狂強奸慣犯
Jesus, Lloyd.
上帝啊 羅伊德
Sorry. It's malicious code that completely takes over their system.
對不起 就是能使系統徹底癱瘓的惡意代碼
It can delete system files
它能夠刪除系統文件
and stop programs.
終止所有的程序
Viruses, worms
病毒 蠕蟲病毒
How do we stop it?
我們怎么才能阻止它?
That's the thing.
這就是問題所在
It's fundamentally invisible you can't stop it.
這個完全是隱形的 你無法阻止它
All of their servers are timing out.
他們所有的服務器都已經超時了
None of them are coming back up.
沒有辦法進行重啟
That's because every time we restart the server the virus replicates itself
這是因為每次我們重新啟動服務器 病毒就會在這時候啟動
during boot up and crashes the host.
加倍 從而破壞主機
How are we supposed to bring up the network if we can't restart the servers?
所以我們怎樣才能救活整個網絡 如果我們不能重啟整個服務器?
We can't.
我們不能
Which is what they wanted.
這就是他們想要的
By defending ourselves, we ended up spreading the virus everywhere.
通過保護自己 我們最后會將將病毒擴散到每個地方
Only thing we can do is we've gotta take the whole system offline
我們能做的就是把整個系統斷開連接
wipe the infected servers, clean, then bring them back up.
然后格式化被感染的服務器 清理干凈 然后再將其重啟備份
You're coming with me.
你跟我來
Yeah.
好
Lloyd.
羅伊德
Tell everybody to start taking everything offline.
告訴所有人開始把所有的服務器斷開連接
On it.
在做了
Uh, the server farm in Dulles. We're gonna need the jet.
服務器都在杜勒斯 我們需要一架飛機
They're booting the network back up.
他們正在啟動服務器的備份
Now, you're downloading the logs, right--
你現在開始下載所有的日志信息 對
Stop. Tell him to stop.
停 告訴他停下來
What?
怎么了?
Don't start the boot sequence.
不要開始啟動序列
You guys missed one.
你們漏了一個
There's an infected server up and running.
這里還有一個在運行的被感染的服務器
What's the ETA before it hits this server?
在它攻擊這個服務器前我們還有多少時間?
The backup server up and running?
備份服務器已經開始運行了?
It's ready, but it's not configured for auto switch.
它準備好了 但是并沒有開始配置自動開關
We need to redirect the traffic, need to switch DNS.
我們需要重新定向所有的數據 然后改變域名
you got this. You got this, you got this,
沒問題的 你搞定的 你能做到的
This is impossible.
這不現實啊
you got this, you got this. You got this,
能做到的 能做到的 你能做到的
It's almost at the back server!
它馬上就到備份服務器了
We still up?
我們還在線上?
We're okay.
我們沒事了
Yeah.
是啊
Hank.
漢克
I'm gonna take a look at the infected server, okay?  Give me a minute
我現在要看一下受感染的服務器  給我點時間 行嗎?
Yeah. Uh...I'll meet you at the elevators.
恩 我在電梯里等著你
They must have left a mark or something.
他們一定會留下一些痕跡
Every hacker loves attention.
每個黑客都渴望被關注
They don't just do DDoS attacks for no reason.
他們才不會沒有原因的用分布式拒絕服務攻擊
This is it.
這就是了
Fsociety.
F社會
Is that supposed to be a joke?
這難道是一個笑話?
This was way too easy. They didn't hide it well at all.
這實在是有點太簡單了 他們并沒有隱藏什么
This note is for me.
這是給我的
They're telling me to leave it here.
他們在告訴我 讓我把它留下來
But why? Doesn't matter.
但是為什么? 這不重要
Time to shut them down.
我們該關掉這些了
Why can't I delete it?
為什么我不能刪除它?
I don't want to delete it. I want it to stay.
我不想要去刪除它 我想要它呆在那里
What's wrong with me?
我這是怎么了?
I'll reconfigure the access to the root directory so only I can use it.
我將會重新配置根目錄的授權 這樣只有我才能使用
And no one will know.
沒人會知道
For you, sir.
給您的 先生
Did you know that I'm gay?
你知道其實我是同性戀嗎?
No.
不
Consider this me coming out to you then, okay?
把這個當成是我對你出柜了 好吧?
It's hard because I don't like to talk about my sex life.
這有點難 因為我不想談論我的性生活
But my partner, he gets very paranoid.
但是我的伴侶 他疑心病很重
He thinks I'm ashamed of
他認為我對此感到羞恥
He wants me to be more public about it, so
他想讓我們的關系更加公開化
Anyway, I'm gay.
不管怎么樣 我是同性戀
Thanks.
謝謝
Yeah.
嗯
Hey, man, don't worry about it.
嘿 先生 不要擔心了
Hackers have a short attention span. They'll get bored, harass someone else.
黑客們很少集中注意力 他們很快就會無聊 然后就會騷擾別的人了
Evil Corp is thinking about leaving us.
邪惡公司正在考慮 跟我們分道揚鑣
And I don't know if I can blame them.
我都不知道該不該怪他們
They could have called their other security teams.
他們本可以找別的安全團隊的
They called you.
但他們找了你
Well, somebody over there likes us
總會有那么些人喜歡我們
but Terry Colby, he's getting the pressure.
但是 泰利 科爾比 他現在壓力很大
and he calls the shots.
是他提出要離開我們的
Evil Corp is 80% of our business.
邪惡公司整個我們生意的80%
If we lose them, it's gonna be it for us.It's gonna be it...
如果我們失去了他們 將會是我們最大的損失 這將會是...
For me.
我的損失
NI feel like I can talk to you.
我覺得 我可以跟你講這些
I mean, more than the others, anyway.
我的意思是 比跟別人講的更多
I'm sure, in a weird way, you'll be happy if we went under.
我確信 從某種程度上講 公司要是倒了 你會很高興的
Oh, come on.
別裝了
I know you hate wearing those stupid shirts.
我知道你不喜歡 穿那些很蠢的襯衫
Gideon?
吉迪恩?
I promise I'll find them.
我向你保證我會找到他們的
Evil Corp service should be back up soon enough.
邪惡公司的服務器應該很快就會恢復
I'll take a look at the dat file.
我會看看那些數字文件
I'll ask my IRC contacts about fsociety when I get home.
等到家之后 我會問問互聯網聊天室的朋友關于F社會的事
I've never seen their name on the boards though.
我永遠都看不到他們的名字 不會在明處看到
They've gotta be new, but they're good.
他們是新手 但是他們非常優秀
Rough night?
今夜過得很艱難吧?
I'm getting off here.
我要下車了
I think you should come with me.
我覺得你應該跟我一起走
But only if you didn't delete it.
但前提是 你沒有刪除它
You deleted it, we got nothing to talk about.
如果你刪了它 我們就沒啥可聊的了
Are you talking to me?
你在跟我說話?
Stand clear of the closing doors, please.
請遠離 正在關閉的門
Who are you?
你是誰
We gotta wait for the Q.
我們在這里等Q號線
Then what?
然后呢?
Then we're going to Brooklyn.
然后我們去布魯克林
Out by Coney Island.
在科尼島附近
Why? What's there?
為什么? 那里有什么?
Obviously you're gonna ask a lot of questions.
很明顯你會問一大堆問題
It's weird what you're doing right now, I get it.
你覺得自己在做的事兒 很奇葩 我懂
I-I can't tell you anything until we get there.
我..我不能告訴你任何事 在我們到那兒之前
Can't smoke in here.
你不能在這兒抽煙
You've been following me.
你一直在跟蹤我
Why?
為什么?
What do you want from me?
你想從我身上得到什么?
My dad was a petty thief.
我父親是個小偷
Never could hold down a job. So, he just robbed,
從來不能老老實實的做一份工作 所以 他就搶劫
convenience stores,shops,small-time stuff.
便利店啦 商店啦 小偷小摸的
One time,he sat me down,he told me something I never forgot.
有一次他坐下來跟我說了一些話 是我終生難忘的
He said, "Everyone steals.
他說 "每個人都會偷東西
"That's how it works.
社會就是這么運作的
"You think people out there are getting exactly What they deserve? No.
你覺得每個人都能得到他們應得的東西么?  不是的
"They're getting paid over or under,
他們要么拿錢太多 要么太少
but someone in the chain always gets bamboozled.
但是總有人遭到欺騙
"I steal, Son,but I don't get caught."
"我是偷東西 兒子 但是我沒有被抓 "
"That's my contract with society.
那是我的社會契約
"Now if you can catch me stealing, I'll go to jail.
如果你能抓到我偷東西 那我就進監獄了
"But if you can't,
但是如果你不能
then I've earned the money."
那我就賺到錢了"
I respected that, man.
我很敬佩他所說的 兄弟
I thought that shit was cool as a little kid.
在我小時候我覺得那種事很酷
A few years after that,
幾年之后
they finally caught him.
他終于被抓了
Sent him to jail. Dies five years later.
被送進了監獄并于五年之后逝世
My respect goes with him.
我的崇敬也隨他而去
I thought he was free doing what he did,
我以為他在做自己的事的時候是自由的
but he wasn't.
但事實并不是這樣的
He was in prison.
他在監獄
Just like you are now,Elliot.
就像你現在一樣 伊利艾特
But I'm gonna break you out.
但是我要把你救出來
Why would you guys actually meet IRL?
你們為什么要碰面?
You remember that hacker group O-Megz?
你記得那個叫O-Megz的黑客團隊么?
They got outed by their own leader to the FBI,and six hackers went to prison for it?
就是那個被自己的隊長舉報 導致6名黑客進監獄的那件事?
You know how they got 'em?
你知道他們怎么被抓的么?
They went on the dude's computer,
警方黑進了一個成員的電腦
tracked 'em all down through emails,VPN sessions,
通過郵件VPN對話 短信
chat messages, texts.
將他們一網打盡
- One guy, and the whole thing comes down. It's what's called - A central point of failure.
- 就因為那一個人 所有的一切都泡湯了 這就叫 - 一顆老鼠屎壞了一鍋湯
Right Because they refused to meet in person,
對 因為他們拒絕彼此親自見面
they compromised each other every time they sent so much as a smiley face.
最終他們一次次發送的笑臉表情符號暴露了他們
The rule here is,
所以這里的規矩就是
it's done here,
就在這兒做事
and only here.
而且只在這兒做事
It ends when you walk out that door,and begins when you walk in.
一切終了于你走出這扇門  開始于你推門進來
Our encryption is the real world.
我們的加密術就是現實世界
How do you talk to each other then?
那你們之間如何交流?
We don't.
我們不交流
We come and go, work on the project when we can.
我們時進時出 在我們有空的時候來進行這個項目
How do you trust them?
那你如何能夠相信他們?
I give them an exercise.
我對每個人都有測試
If they pass, they join us. If they fail
如果他們通過了 那就加入我們 如果他們沒通過...
The DDoS attack last night,
那么昨晚的分布式拒絕服務攻擊
you were testing me.
就是你在測試我嘍
You said there was a project.
你說過你們有個項目
-What's the project? -That'll come later.
- 是什么項目? - 那件事過會兒再議
I just wanted you to see the place.
我現在只是想讓你來看看這個地方
There's not much you can do without a CPU.
要是沒有中心處理器 你也巧婦難為無米之炊
I'm crazy.
我瘋了
I have to be crazy because that didn't just happen, right?
我一定是瘋了因為剛才的一切的確是發生了 對么?
This is a delusion. Is this a delusion?
這是都是幻想  這是幻想么?
Shit, I'm a schizo.
該死 我有精神分裂癥了
Have I really lost it this time?
我這次是真的迷失了么?
No, no. Last night happened. It was real.
不 不 昨晚發生的事的確是真的
Angela called me. I was at AllSafe.
安吉拉給我打電話了 我是去了全安全公司
Evil Corp's servers were compromised.
邪惡公司的服務器的確癱瘓了
Those are facts,not delusions
那些都是事實 不是幻覺
I know. I know, I know I realize I'm saying all of this to an imaginary person,
我知道的 我知道的 我知道的 我知道我是在跟一個幻想中的人在說這些事兒
but I created you.
但是是我創造了你
I didn't create this.
我可沒造這一堆破事兒
Oh, thank God you're here.
噢 還好你回來了
I was just about to go wait in the Starbucks.
我正要去星巴克等你呢
You live in a bad neighborhood. Do you know that?
你住的這個社區很爛 你知道么?
I do know that.
我知道
Do you want to get high and watch your favorite movie?
你想喝高點然后一起看你喜歡的電影么?
Oh, you saved our asses last night
喔 你昨晚救了我們
I thought Gideon was definitely gonna fire me.
我本以為吉迪恩一定會炒了我的
Where have you been?
你去哪兒了?
I thought you'd be sleeping.
我以為你會在睡覺呢
I--yeah, I fell asleep on the train.
我..嗯 我在地鐵上睡著了
That sounds like such a lie,
這聽上去就像是謊話
but, whatever. I don't want to get into that right now.
但是 不管怎么樣 我現在不想知道
So you want to do this?
所以我們到底要不要喝酒看電影??
I miss Qwerty.
我都想庫爾提了
I hope she still loves me.
希望她還愛我
Shit.
見鬼
She wasn't supposed to be here, okay?
她不該出現在這兒的 好么?
Give me a minute and I'll get rid of her.
給我一分鐘我會處理掉她的
That's okay. Um...
沒事的  呃...
This is great.
這挺棒的
-Elliot, I'm happy for you. -No, it's not like that.
- 伊利艾特 我很替你高興 - 不 事情不是這樣的
Well, maybe it should be,you know?
嗯 也許其實也不錯 你知道么?
It's good that you're...dating.
你在約會其實...挺好的
Well, I'll see you on Monday.
嗯 我們周一再見嘍
We can do movie night next time.
我們下次再一起看電影吧
I promise, okay?
我保證 好么?
Yeah.
嗯
Have fun.
玩的開心喲
Mm, Elliot?
嗯..伊利艾特?
Oh, shit. Is it Wednesday?
噢 混蛋 現在已經是周三了么?
-Shayla. -I have to move my car.
- 夏拉 - 我得去換邊停車了
Shayla, leave.
夏拉 離開這里
Now.
馬上
No mention of Mr. Robot anywhere.
從來沒有關于機器人先生的信息哪里都沒有
No mention of F-society.
也沒有關于"F社會"的信息
Not on any of the hacker boards.
任何黑客論壇上都沒有
Not on IRC, forums, blogs,
網上交談 論壇 博客上通通沒有
no one's heard of them.
沒有人聽說過他們
Property was owned by Fun Society Amusement, LLC for 13 years.
那片地產13年來歸開心社會娛樂有限公司所有
Owner was shot a killed a year and a half ago.
產權人在一年半前被殺了
No owner since.
自此便成為無主地
And the ownership history before that is sparse to nonexistent.
而且在此之前的所有權歷史信息根本不存在
This guy is good. Very good.
這個人很強啊 相當強
Doesn't matter.
不管了
Their arcade network's IP is in the dat file
他們的網絡地址都在那個數據文件里
That'll be enough to turn them in.
用來舉報他們足夠了
What's your ask, Mr. Robot?
你有何企圖 機器人先生?
Hey, man,
嘿 兄弟
where's your boss?
你老大在哪?
Okay, cut the bullshit.
好吧 別說廢話
When are you going to give us access to the root directory?
你什么時候才能給我們根目錄的權限?
What?
什么?
Dude, come on. I wrote that rootkit.
省省吧 老兄 我寫的那個隱匿公式
I still have to put Colby's IP in the dat file.
我還得在那個數據文件上加上科爾比的網絡地址才行
Dickhead.
傻蛋
Elliot! Good news.
伊利艾特! 好消息
I scored the last bag of Twinkies from Gristedes.
我搶到了最后一袋超市的夾餡面包
You want one?
來一個么?
She just called me a dickhead.
她剛才居然叫我傻蛋
Yeah, that's Darlene.
嗯哼 那是戴琳
Hey, you like Ferris wheels?
嘿 你喜歡摩天輪么?
Ah, it's beautiful.
噢 太美了
Gets better the higher up you go, you know?
越高風景越好 你知道么?
Oh, I love it up here.
噢 我太喜歡這兒了
You like it?
你喜歡么?
I'm here to tell you I'm turning you in.
我來是告訴你 我要去舉報你們
I'm giving them all the information.  -Let me tell you why you're really here.
-我要給他們你們所有的信息 -讓我來告訴你 你來的真正原因
You're here because you sense something wrong with the world.
你來這兒是因為 你感覺這個世界有什么不對
Something you can't explain.
一些你無法解釋的事
But you know it controls you and everyone you care about.
但是你知道它控制了你 和你身邊你在乎的所有人
What are you talking about?
你在說什么呢?
Money.
金錢
Money hasn't been real since we got off the gold standard. It's become virtual.
自從我們廢除金本位制以來  錢都不再是實體了 變成虛擬的了
Software.
是種軟件
The operating system of our world.
這是我們這個世界運行的機制
And, Elliot, we are on the verge
還有 伊利艾特 我們馬上就要
of taking down this virtual reality.
拿下這種虛擬現實了
Think about it.
想想吧
What if you could take down one conglomerate?
如果你能拿下一個企業那會是怎樣?
A conglomerate so deeply entrenched in the world's economy,
一個與世界經濟緊密相關的大企業
that too big to fail doesn't even come close to describing it.
那可是大成功啊 我甚至都沒辦法描述它
You want to create another financial meltdown
你想再創造一場金融危機嗎
like the one we just had,but way worse.
就像我們剛剛經歷的這場 但比它還糟糕
Yeah, why would I want that?
是啊 我又為什么想要這么做呢?
Everyone would lose their money.
每個人都會損失他們的錢財
What if I told you that this conglomerate just so happens to own 70% of the global consumer credit industry?
如果我告訴你這個企業恰巧持有全球70%消費者信用行業的股份呢?哈?
If we hit their data center just right,
如果我們能準確地黑入他們的數據中心
we could systematically format all the servers
我們就能系統地格式化所用用戶的資料
-including backup. -That would erase all
- 包括備份 - 這樣會清除掉...
All the debt we owe them.
我們欠的所有債
Every record of every credit card, loan, and mortgage would be wiped clean.
每一筆信用卡 貸款 抵押的記錄都會被清除
It would be impossible to reinforce outdated paper records.
強化那些過時的紙質記錄是不可能的
It would all be gone.
所有一切都煙消云散
The single biggest incident of wealth redistribution in history.
人類歷史上最大的財產重新分配事件
Evil Corp. The conglomerate.
邪惡公司 你說的那個公司
That's why you picked me.
這就是你選我的原因啊
Because I work at AllSafe.
因為我在全安全工作
Tomorrow, AllSafe is going to get a visit from the FBI
明天 全安全將會有聯邦調查局
and the U.S. Cyber Command.
和美國網絡司令部的人到訪
You are going to modify the dat file
你去修改那個數字文件
and put Colby's terminal IP address in there.
把科爾比的IP終端地址放進去
Terry Colby?
泰利 科爾比嗎?
You're gonna frame him?
你準備陷害他?
No one's gonna believe that.
沒人會相信的
I met him, he's a moron.
我見過他 他就是個腦殘
So are the FBI.
FBI不也是么
Even if they don't believe he did it,
即使他們不相信是他做的
they'll believehe gave someone access to it.
他們也會相信是他幫了別人做的
Yeah, he'll just go to jail.
是啊 然后他就是會進監獄而已
What good will that do?
那有什么用啊?
You don't take down a conglomerate by shooting them in the heart.
要扳倒一個大的企業集團是不能瞄準核心一擊斃命的
That's the thing about conglomerates,
大企業集團就是這樣
they don't have hearts.
他們沒有核心
You take them down limb by limb.
要一點一點的瓦解掉
And as they unravel,
隨著企業慢慢被拆散
their illusion of control unravels.
他們一手掌控的錯覺也會瓦解
Who are you?
你是誰?
That'll come later.
你以后再知道也不遲
Right now, you have a lot to think about.
現在 你有很多事需要好好想想
You have to change the dat file
你得修改那個數據文件
and put Colby's IP in there.
然后把科爾比的IP輸進去
You do that,
如果你那樣做的話
you have set in motion the largest revolution the world will ever see.
那就是發動了一場史上最大型的革命
Neil Diamond's ?
尼爾·戴蒙德演唱 ?
If you go away ?
若你離去 ?
On this summer day ?
在這夏日里 ?
Then you might as well ?
不如帶著太陽 ?
take the sun away ?
一同離去 ?
All the birds that flew ?
夏日天空 ?
In a summer sky ?
鳥兒翱翔 ?
When our love was new ?
那時我們愛如蜜糖 ?
And our hearts were high ?
心氣昂揚 ?
When the day was young ?
那時白晝伊始 ?
And the night was long ?
夜晚漫長 ?
And the moon stood still ?
月色靜靜 ?
For the night birds song ?
鳥聲輕唱 ?
If you go away ?
若你離去 ?
But if you stay ?
若你留下 ?
I'll make you a day ?
我會陪在你身邊 ?
Like no day's been ?
讓你的一天 ?
Or will be again ?
永生難忘 ?
We'll sail on the sun ?
我們在陽光下起航 ?
We'll ride on the rain ?
我們在細雨中前行 ?
We'll talk to the trees ?
我們與樹木私語 ?
And worship the wind ?
我們沐浴微風 ?
Then if you go ?
如此你仍離開 ?
I'll understand ?
我會明白 ?
Leave me just enough love ?
留你足夠的愛 ?
To fill up my hand ?
填滿我雙手空白 ?
If you go away ?
若你離去 ?
As I know you must ?
我知道你必須離去 ?
There'll be nothing left ?
這世上我 ?
In the world to trust ?
生無可戀 ?
Just an empty room ?
只余房間 ?
Full of empty space ?
空蕩一片 ?
Like the empty look ?
正如我所見 ?
I see on your face ?
你一臉茫然 ?
Can I tell you now ?
如今我是否可以坦白 ?
As you turn to go ?
當你轉身離開 ?
I'll be dying slowly ?
我將慢慢老去 ?
Till your next hello ?
直到你我再次會面 ?
If you go away ?
若你離去 ?
If you go away... ?
若你離去... ?
So, what do we got?
那么 我們開始吧?
So, if you'll take a look at the first page of your agenda--
你們看一下日程的第一頁
You're the one who stopped the hack.
是你阻止了黑客入侵
You know, the gals in analysis said this was a tough one.
你們知道么 分析部的姑娘們說這次挺難搞的
All things being equal,
正常情況下
it should have shut us down for days, so...
這次入侵可能會讓我們當掉好多天 所以...
you did good.
干得漂亮
Okay.
恩
We should start with our account executive, Angela.
我們應該先從客戶經理 安吉拉開始
Okay, we first noticed the breach
好的 我們初次注意到被攻擊
2:07 A.M. Eastern Standard on Friday night.
是在周五晚上 是東部標準時間上午兩點零七分
You mean, Saturday?
你是說周六?
Sorry, yes, technically, Saturday morning.
抱歉 是的 準確的講 是周六早晨
Yeah, okay, Angela,
好的 安吉拉
that's what we're here for. The technicals.
我們在這開會就是為了這個 準確的技術細節
Right.
好的
Yes.
恩
Anyway, he arrived at the office35 and I instru--
總之 他在35分的時候到達辦公室 然后我告訴
Okay, wait, wait, wait.
好吧 等等 停一下
So that's almost a half hour after the initial breach.
這么說那已經是初次被攻擊之后半個小時了
Why didn't anyone pipe in from their laptops?
為什么沒有人用筆記本接進來?
- It's not protocol - It wouldn't have been secure
- 規定流程不是那樣的 - 那樣并不安全
if someone terminaled in on this.
如果讓人通過終端登入這個
It was the smarter move to have someone come in
等有人過來 然后通過安全線路
-so they can log in on a secure line. -Exactly.
- 登錄是更好地做法 - 正是如此
Then Lloyd was able to -Just--just actually, just one second.
- 那樣羅伊德就能 - 等 等等 打斷一下--
- Yeah.
恩
You know, I, uh,
你知道的 我 呃
I always loved this view.
我一直很喜歡這里的風景
Now that that's taken care of,
現在 既然那件事已經解決了
let's pick it up where we left off.
那我們就繼續之前的話題吧
What happened to Angela?
安吉拉怎么了?
She knows more about what happened.
她更清楚到底發生了什么
She's not going to work out for us, not on this level.
她對我們不會有很有用的 起碼在這個層面不會
We need to stick to the more tech savvy here.
我們現在需要堅持從更技術的角度看
Now, let's get to the heart of this thing
好了 咱們來討論一下這件事的核心
because I can't sit hereand look through a packet for the next 20 minutes.
我不能一直坐在這花上20分鐘慢慢瀏覽文件
All right, just who did this?
好了 到底是誰做的?
Is it that hard?
就這么難?
Who did this?
誰做的?
I found the configuration file of the rootkit with a pattern of IP addresses.
我發現這個惡意程序配置文件的IP地址有固定的模式
Once you decrypt it, you'll know where the hack came from
一但能夠破譯就會知道黑客在哪里
19 days.
19天
No news, no arrests,no revolution
沒有新聞 沒有拘捕 也沒有革命
No FBI, Colby, Evil Corp.
沒有FBI 科爾比和邪惡公司
No Mr. Robot.
沒有機器人先生
No fsociety.
沒有F社會
I need to take my mind off things.
我需要轉移一下注意力
Hello.
你好
Hi, this is Sam from Bank of E security fraud department
嗨 我是電子安全銀行詐騙處理部門的山姆
Unfortunately I have to inform you N that your account's been compromised.
很不幸地通知您 您的賬戶被盜用了
What? What happened?
什么? 怎么回事?
First before I can answer any questions I need to verify some information
在我回答任何問題之前 我需要核實一下您的信息
Are you still at 306 Hawthorne Avenue?
您現在是否仍居住在霍桑大街306號？
Yes. Apartment 2C.
是的 門牌號2C
Great. And your security question,favorite baseball team?
好的 您的安全問題 最喜歡的棒球隊?
Um, Yankees.
呃 洋基隊
-I don't remember this being a security question. -And lastly, your pet's name?
-我不記得有這么個安全問題啊 -最后一個問題 您的寵物叫什么?
Um, Flipper.
呃 鰭鰭
Who am I speaking to?Can I get your name and number?
你是誰?能說一下你的名字和號碼嗎?
With those details plus Na dictionary brute-force attack,it'll take my program maybe two minutes to crack his password.
掌握了那些詳細信息再加上強力攻擊  我的程序大概2分鐘就可以破解他的密碼
What I wouldn't give to be normal.
我愿放棄一切只為做一個普通的人
To live in that bubble,
生活在美好的幻想中
the reality of the naive.
天真之人的現實
That's how I justify this.
我就是這樣看待這件事的
To keep their optimism intact.
為了保護他們樂觀的赤子之心
To protect them.
為了保護他們
How? He's too old to have a complicated password
怎么可能? 他年紀那么大了密碼肯定不會很復雜
It had to have been a combination of these things.
肯定是這些信息的某種組合
I'm missing something,I'm missing something,I'm missing something.
我漏掉了什么東西 我漏掉了什么東西 我漏掉了什么東西
Michael Hansen N isn't his real name.
邁克爾 漢森 不是他的真名
Lenny Shannon?
列尼 香農?
Michael Hansen?
邁克爾 漢森?
Which one are you playing tonight?
你今晚扮演的是哪個?
You're going to stops eeing Krista.
你不能繼續和克里斯塔交往了
What the fuck...
搞什么鬼
You're going to break up with her.You're never going to see her again.
你要和她分手 你不會再見到她
You're the guy that used my phone
你就是那個用了我電話的家伙
You cheated on your current wife with seven different women.
你劈腿你現任老婆和7個女人鬼混
I got digital proof of all of it.
我有所有的數據證明
Ashley Madison, online escorts,fake Facebook pages
阿什利 麥迪遜 在線招妓 假的臉書頁面
I own it all.
這些數據我都有
And if you don't stop seeing her,
如果你不和她分手
your wife will know everything along with the police.
你妻子就會知道所有的事情 還有警察也會知道
The police?
警察?
Yeah, one of the escorts was 15.
是啊 有一個應召女郎只有15歲
That 15 part I made up,
15歲的部分是我編的
but he did have a proclivity for young escorts that helped the lie.
但是他確實有偏好年輕女孩的傾向  所以幫我圓了謊
But I'm not gonna do any of that
但是我不會那樣做的
as long as you break up with Krista.
只要你和克里斯塔分手
Tonight.
今晚就分
Done.
成交
You're also gonna tell her the truth.
你還得告訴她事情的真相
That you're married,cheat on your wife,
告訴她你已經結婚了 你對自己的妻子不忠
you hire hookers.
花錢嫖娼
That you never had any intention of being serious with her.
你從來沒有任何想與她認真交往的念頭
Why?
為什么?
That would destroy her. She thinks that...
那樣會毀了她的 她以為...
We're in love.
我們是相愛的
Exactly. Krista needs to avoid dickheads like you in the future.
正是如此 以后克里斯塔需要避開像你這種混蛋
Her radar needs fixing.
她探測男人的雷達需要修一修了
I'll know if you skip any detail.
如果你漏掉任何細節我都會知道的
So don't.
所以不要有遺漏
And one more thing...
還有一件事...
I'm gonna need something from you.
我還需要你的一件東西
Come on.
來吧
I like you, Flipper.
我挺喜歡你的 鰭鰭
You're cool.
你很酷
I never want to be right about my hacks,
我從來都不希望我的侵入是對的
but people always find a way to disappoint.
但是人們總有各種各樣的方式讓我大失所望
Michael Hansen now gets filed away among the others.
邁克爾 漢森現在已經和其他人一樣被歸檔了
Forever buried in my digital cemetery.
永久封存在我的數字檔案中
The look of disillusionment.
一切幻滅的表情
He told her. She cried all night.
他告訴她了 她哭了一整晚
Now comes the sadness.
現在到了感傷的階段
I don't like seeing her sad.
我不喜歡看她傷心
- You okay?- Sorry.
- 你還好嗎?- 抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉
Go on.
繼續吧
I think Angela blames me for what happened at the Evil Corp meeting.
我覺得安吉拉認為邪惡公司會議上發生的情況應該怪我
What do I do? I need to talk to her.
我該怎么辦? 我得和她談談
I think you just answered your own question.
你剛剛不是回答了自己的問題
Talk to her.
和她談談
She won't respond to any of my texts or emails.
她不回我的短信或者是郵件
Then go to her in person.
那就當面去找她
Tell her you need to talk
告訴她你想和她談談
Communication is key,Elliot.
溝通是關鍵 伊利艾特
Real human interaction.
真正的人際互動
That's what's important for you right now.
這才是現在對你來說真正重要的
Hey. Do you-- Do you think we can talk?
嘿 你 你覺得我們現在能談談嗎?
- What?
什么?
You won't talk to me.
你不愿跟我說話
You haven't talked to mes ince the meeting.
自從開完會之后 你就沒和我說過話
I don't want to talk to you because I feel embarrassed
我不想和你說話 因為我覺得很尷尬
every time I think about what happened.
每當我一想起所發生的事情
Okay?
行了嗎?
It's fine. I'll get over it.
沒事的 我會克服的
- It's been three weeks. - I have to get back to work.
- 都三個禮拜了 - 我得繼續工作了
You're just going to ignore me? -You didn't have to stick up for me in there
- 你就準備這樣無視我? - 你在會上的時候不必幫我說話的
I know that you were just trying to help,
我知道你僅僅是想幫我
just don't do it again.
不過不要再那樣做了
Even if I'm losing.
即使我撐不下去了
Let me lose, okay?
那就讓我輸了吧 好嗎?
Don't look confused.
不要露出迷茫的表情
Just say it.
答應就好了
"Okay."
說"好的"
Okay.
好的
Elliott.
伊利艾特
FBI agents claim that Colby either used hacking groups or worked in conjunction with them
FBI特工稱科爾比不是雇傭了黑客組織就是與其合作
After a long and exhaustive investigation,sources close to the FBI
經過漫長而詳盡的調查 FBI方已掌握證據
have confirmed the hacks were in part tied to Colby's terminal.
證明黑客入侵事件與科爾比的終端有部分關聯
It's happening, it's happening,it's happening, it's happening.
發生了 發生了 發生了 發生了
Sir, step inside the car.
先生 請上車
Step insidethe vehicle now.
現在就上車
Go ahead.
請吧
Sir, go on in.
先生 請
Bon soir, Elliot.
晚上好 伊利艾特
Please tell me you're seeing this, too.
拜托請告訴我你也看到了這個